Cheers!
Men like him can't help
themselves from dreaming.
He gazes towards tomorrow,
eyes are gleaming.
But every day a dreamer
fights against reality.
It seems a struggle to be free.
If I were alone, I might surrender.
Weight's too heavy for me.
When I hear him say it,
even I can't believe.
Today is the day, we'll
bury all our sorrow.
Time to raise the sails,
they'll tell our tales.
Through every tomorrow.
Today is the day, we're
aiming towards a new dawn.
And all our doubts are gone.
Let's move along.
Cause it's time to sail away.
For the new world.
Where our dreams will all come true.
Oh, so long.
What the?
Huh?
Bunch of fools!
Why did you have to get
all sentimental like that?
Now we can't cash it on his bounty!
If you don't get out of our way,
we'll arrest every last one of you!
I'd like to see you try.
Just let the man play his
rock and roll, damn it!
Hey, what's going on over there?
It's out of control,
I'll tell you that much!
The Navy came to arrest Soul King during
his show when I was there to rioting!
Looks like he made his escape, though.
You skinless traitor!
I'm gonna make you pay!
Anyway, that's not the big story here.
Soul King is actually a pirate
known as the Humming Swordsman.
He's one of the Straw Hats!
Thank you for the ride, my friend.
And that was impeccable
timing, I must say.
You can thank Chaka for
putting all this together.
Your friends should be
waiting for you at Grove 42.
I'm so eager to see them
again my heart is beating out
of my chest kidding obviously
my chest is an empty void.
So here's the skinny brother?
Luffy's on the island.
Somewhere but the Navy's
about to close in and the
rest of the crew is headed
to grove 42 meet us there!
Roger that Franky.
What's up great you mean
you weren't listening?
Well, let's see
Navy, come here.
Us pirates, ship.
Run away.
Is that clear enough?
Why are you talking like that?
Did you hit your head or something?
Sorry.
I just thought I'd speak on
your level for once. Huh?
All right, then.
After this, stupid cook, die.
Real funny.
Anyway, you know what all that
racket over there is about?
Huh?
You, right.
All right, that's enough yakking. Listen!
Turns out Sanji and Zoro found
one of the guys who insulted me.
In fact, he's here with us right now.
Look at this little punk.
I'm gonna beat a lesson into
him with my own two hands.
Because when you piss me
off, then things get ugly.
And let this be a lesson
to all of you, too.
If you ever cross me, if
you ever disrespect me,
you're going to end up
just like this chump.
Don't forget who's the boss of this crew.
Is that perfectly clear?
You're in that bounty somehow, and
it wasn't by playing News Nights.
What's with this guy? Zoro? Sanji?
A friend of yours or something?
I don't think he likes me.
We've got you surrounded.
Nobody move an inch.
Straw Hat Luffy, you and the rest
of your crew are under arrest.
Surrender immediately. The Navy?
And don't bother running away.
We blocked off every exit in Grove 46.
You guys leave with us or you're
going to leave in a body bag.
My disguise is perfect.
How did the Navy know I was here?
Why would you think
that this was about you?
Captain, please tell
me we're not all dead.
Stop flipping out.
We'll be just fine.
Why do you think we
recruited all these guys?
We've got pirates with hundred million
bounties here, but this is scary!
Then sit back and watch.
Caribou Europe use that marine as a shield
and make us a path out of this dump?
Wait what marine we sent
a scout here earlier
that looks like he was
taken captive damn it.
That's not good
Although that would be
terribly convenient.
I'm afraid it simply won't do!
Why not?
Because he told me he
hadn't called the Navy yet.
And that makes him a filthy little liar.
Caribou, no!
That crazy bastard!
Who's the captain here, damn it?
Oh, well, so much for that plan.
You high and mighty type
seem to think it's all right
to lie to someone if
they're a so-called bad guy.
Well, I object to that.
I guess they're not surrendering, huh?
Should have figured as much.
George, show the pirates no mercy!
Good luck!
Our boss is Straw Hat Luffy.
He's not going to lose to
a bunch of chumps like you.
Let's go!
If you've got a plan, I'd hurry!
Listen to your captain, you
guys are pissing me off!
That guy just said that I was his boss,
but I've never even seen him before.
I do not have time to deal
with your nonsense right now.
Aim for the captain in charge!
I know you.
You're lip service Daddy.
Your bounty's 88 million.
You may be idiots, but at
least you're not cowards.
Don't let him intimidate you!
Holy crap!
He's got a bounty of 92 million!
That's gashed Albion!
We'll take him down!
Justice is on our side!
The ground is soaked with
the blood of hypocrites.
Its overwhelming stench makes me so sick.
A 210 million bounty, wet-haired
caribou, too late to surrender now!
Oh, damn it, no one said
he had a Devil Fruit power!
Why don't we all slow down a bit?
Haven't you heard that stress
can lead to an early grave?
My sword!
What?
Pass-a-bistas!
Oh, hell.
Nobody told me they were going to be here.
I kind of want to beat
up those robot guys,
but Hancock said to stay out
of trouble, so I guess I won't.
Those things that vaporize the mustache
off your stupid face, you nutbag!
Monkey D.
Luffy has been identified.
Commence attack.
Those things are aiming straight at me.
Can I even run or am I just dead?
I was hoping I'd get to
rumble with them someday.
Lip service, Daddy,
identified and subdued.
Sustains no damage.
Searching for next target.
Captain Daddy!
Follow the pacifistas!
Capture every pirate in your path!
Dodie's that cold.
A bounty like that, and these guys
took him down in only one shot?
We're screwed.
Hang up, wait for us!
I ain't waiting for nobody!
The thing took out Daddy!
I don't see the chance!
Straw Hat, do something!
You're the only one who can stop him now!
I hate to beg, Captain, but your whole
crew is about to get blown up over here!
There's no more left to run!
Oh crap he's gone.
Where is Straw Hat?
They keep calling for their captain! But.
My side is killing me.
The lasers are gonna kill you!
Get your fat ass!
Out of my way!
Who is this idiot?
He's here.
Captain Luffy!
Am I mistaken or did they
call you Captain Luffy?
Why wouldn't they call me that?
I mean, you realize...
Who you're talking to
right now, don't you?
Go get out of my way before I grab
your intestines and pull them out!
Your ear!
I'd run if I were you!
You're face to face
with the son of dragon!
The revolutionary!
That means I'm the
grandson of the hero! Garb!
Oh and my bounty!
It clucks into 400 million berries!
Turn on Straw Hat!
You human pile of garbage!
Not even close!
That guy just took out Straw Hat!
So that's it!
Fools!
They thought that they could join the
Straw Hats and enter the New World!
PX5!
Who is this imposter?
Confirmed.
He is triple-tongued D 'Amato Black, a
pirate with a 26 million Barry Bounty.
What?
He's only worth 26 million.
That means...
He's afraid!
Look at guys, the jig is up!
What the hell are we supposed to do now?
It's bad enough this guy tricked us, but
now we got the Navy called on us too!
Guess the real Straw
Hat is dead after all.
What the hell?
You mean Straw Hat
didn't get fat and gross?
This guy was just fat
and gross to begin with?
Wait, what?
That fat gross guy was
pretending to be me?
And Sanji and Zoro?
They looked real, but I
guess they were fakes too.
Wow, this is blowing my mind.
I gotta get out of here.
I know you aren't real Straw Hats,
and you're just victims of this
fool, but you're still pirates.
That means a lot of
you are coming with us.
And although I cannot imagine why, the
real Straw Hat is here somewhere, too.
When we entered the area, Pucci detected
him on the stage with the impostors.
Fire on Straw Hat, Pucci!
That was close!
You almost blew up all my lunches!
What did food ever do to you?
Uh... Huh? Oof! It's...
It's really him, isn't it?
That's Straw Hat Loopy!
The real Straw Hat was here
and we didn't even know!
Nothing has changed, man!
We came here to capture Straw
Hat and that's what we're doing!
Sir!
So there you are!
I had enough of you the
last time we fought.
I'm just trying to set sail.
I'm not supposed to start any trouble.
Oh, it's no trouble, but
you won't be setting sail.
Unlike two years ago, I'm an
official Navy officer now.
That means I'm taking you in
if it's the last thing I do.
Pucci, fire!
Is that all?
What?
Second gear!
You're way too slow!
Come, come, jet-pasta!
This is worse than I thought.
He can use Haki now.
He made a passive beast up
and all it took was one horse.
So long.
So I have a feeling I'm gonna
see you again somewhere.
Get back here and fight me!
Don't let him go, man!
Hurry!
Yes, sir!
Hey! Luffy! Luffy! Should've known!
All I had to do was follow the
explosions and I knew I'd find you!
Okay, do for real this time!
And Zora's not even fat! Way to go!
Roronoa and Blackfoot!
I should've known they were still alive!
R .I .P.
on summon attack!
Get lost!
I'm the one who got him. Keep dreaming!
My kick broke his neck!
It's the real Strawheads!
They're monsters!
The big ones were
nothing like this at all!
By the way, Luffy, you're number nine.
Nobody cares!
Would you give up on that?
Everyone's waiting at the sunny.
Let's get moving.
Got it!
We're not missing this chance!
Every last Marine!
After them!
Man, it's been forever, huh?
I bet everyone's so cool now.
I can't wait to see!
What happened? Let's go!
It can't be!
That's Star King's really!
I came to check on you, but it
seems you have this under control.
In fact, you're even stronger
than when I left you.
Finally time to see your friends.
You've been waiting for long enough.
Thanks, really! For real!
You did so much for me
these past two years!
No need to get sappy on me. Just go.
One last thing!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna be the king.
Of the pirates.
You hear me?
What are you doing?
Hurry up and capture them already!
Gotta move Luffy.
We appreciate the help Rayleigh.
Well, we're off.
Thanks again for everything.
See ya.
I'm out of here.
Good luck.
They're on the move!
After them!
Let him get away!
Let nothing stop you
from reaching the top!
The Straw Hats are making
a beeline for Grove 42!
Catch them at any cost!
It's our King Barrel!
Why don't you just let the boy sail?
He's been out of the
game, so take it easy.
That's an intense line.
If you think that's intense, then
why don't you try crossing it?
Whoa! That's a lot!
You really went all out!
What's inside?
It's our food stock!
I bought in bulk because
I'm sure everyone's
stomachs have gotten bigger
over these two years.
This should keep us all happy for a while.
Good thinking!
They haven't had your
cooking in way too long!
Over here!
We found them!
Crap, they get ahead of us somehow.
Looks like we're gonna have
to fight our way through.
Charge in!
We got this!
I'm as worthless as a flea.
What's wrong?
Get up before - I'll be a tick. Oh no!
Ow!
What happened to their morale?
I...
I'm nothing but a louse.
This sure looks familiar.
How did I know it was you
guys causing that ruckus?
So typical.
You're fooling around with the Navy
when you should have been gone long ago.
Whoa!
Well, aren't you a sight for sore eyes!
Speak for yourself.
If you were smart, you
would have bailed by now.
You wouldn't even be here if it
weren't for me, so don't start, mister!
Who knows where you would
have wound up on your own!
The least you could do is be gracious!
She's an actual woman with real-life
girly parts! Of course I am!
What the hell is your damage, you freak!
Alright, enough of this.
You guys need to get moving.
There's a Navy ships nearby,
so you're running out of time!
If you don't get out of here
soon, you'll never escape!
Look who's here!
Usopp!
Nami!
Robin!
Alright!
You're here!
What a surprise!
I didn't think you'd abandon stardom!
Attaboy!
Nothing could keep me from coming back.
I've missed you all so.
I see that you two have only
grown lovelier in our time apart.
With all that in mind, there's
something I need to know.
It's already song time, huh?
Please, Nami, may I look at your panties?
No way in hell!
I never let you look
at them two years ago.
Why would I let you see them now?
I was just excited to see you.
It made my soul shake, and
it's still shaking right now.
In fact, it's about to leak out of my ear.
I didn't think you could have a
muscle spasm without any muscles.
Seriously?
How is it none of you have
grown up after all this time?
Rejection aside, I was actually expecting
to be the last one here. Don't worry.
Chopper is off looking
for a missing companion.
Huh? Hey!
Talk about perfect timing!
GUYS!
Hey!
Told you I would find him!
Luffy! Zoro! ZACHI!
Hey!
Together again!
I've been waiting for this day!
And everyone looks stronger!
I like it!
It feels like it's been forever!
Looks like we're the last...
Hi, guys!
Huh?
He's everything!
Thanks a lot for the ride.
Tell everyone back in the
birdie kingdom I say hi.
How is he?
Has the bleeding stopped yet?
Not one, but two beautiful women
in front of me. Stay with me, man.
Don't give up yet.
It's no good, Chopper!
He's getting paler by the second!
You look so cool, Franky!
Yeah, you think so? Good.
But even if you didn't, I could
change my style at will, Mecca.
Mecca!
Okay, focus.
This is no time to be fooling around.
We need to get out of here while we
can before the Navy's on top of us.
No, it looks like we're too late.
I see three Navy ships.
If we don't do something fast,
we're going to be dead in the water.
Fire!
Sink that ship at all costs!
Slave...
No!
What?
We stopped in midair.
We... Captain.
It's the Kuja Pirates!
Answer me this, knaves.
Which one of you had the audacity to
place your disgusting ship in my path?
That flag, it can't be.
You know it?
That's the Kuja symbol.
They're a strong crew of Amazonians
led by one of the Seven Warlords.
You're joking, right?
Not at all.
Her name is Boa Hancock.
They say anyone who lays eyes
on her will be enamored by
her beauty and turned to stone
unless she grants you mercy.
Oh, I can see why beauty
starts and ends with her.
If I had eyes, they'd be sparkling.
Wow, she's a real life goddess.
Is she really that fine? Let me see.
My goddess.
Where gotta find her?
I want to see. I wanna. I wanna.
He's as hard as a rock.
Hancock said she wasn't coming here.
We order you to move
your ship out of the way.
You're interfering with
official Navy business.
It's your ship that's in my way.
So I suppose it's you that's
interfering with official Navy business.
Uh, that's really an immature argument.
I get what I want.
Go, Luffy.
I've bought you some time.
Circulus, I could die of ecstasy.
Looks like we have an opening.
Let's set sail.
Do you know that warlord or something?
Yeah.
I made friends with her when that
bear guy sent me to Amazon Lily.
You mean the legendary
island where only women live?
I never believed it was a real place.
You've been palling around
with the pirate empress?
Come clean now!
You weren't really training at all
these past two years, were you?
What else would I have been doing?
Damn, it's not fair.
That would have been a dream come true.
What's his problem?
Wow.
So those are Luffy's friends.
I've never seen so many strange
creatures together before.
There's one, two, three, four.
They look like such a fun crew.
Okay, everyone in position to set sail.
Yes, there's one.
What's the matter, Usopp?
Something just occurred to me.
You never said you beat
the Navy soldiers inland.
We didn't.
We just flew past them,
but we could hear them shouting
from behind us in the distance.
Then what could be stopping
them from coming after us?
This is Backup Unit
Platoon 3. Do you copy?
We read you.
What's happening?
We are unable to reach Grove 42.
What? Why?
Well, because there are giant bugs
currently halting our advance.
Wait, giant what?
These things are monsters.
Shoot it!
I won't let anyone get in the
way of Usoppun going adventuring.
Men don't shed tears when they part ways.
Good luck, Usoppun.
Who cares why they're coming after us?
The worse their lives are,
the better ours will be.
Heh, it's time to get out of here.
Nami, lead the way! You got it.
Alright.
This is Platoon 4.
Afraid I have bad news.
All our gunpowder has been
ruined by a sudden rain shower.
What?
That is impossible!
The forecast for Sabaoni Archipelago
today is clear and sunny!
Thunder would be excessive.
After all, we don't want
to scare the civilians now.
I wasn't expecting those bubbles
to give us so much grief.
Bubbles or not, you can't
complain about the wind.
No, sir.
That breeze got us where we
wanted to be right on schedule.
Of course it did.
When it's something for Nami,
she gets nothing but the best.
We'll miss you on Weatheria, young lady.
But get out there and give it your all.
Hey, what's it doing?
Are you sure this is supposed to inflate?
Whoa!
Now our boat's got a bubble roof!
This is how it works.
A ship that is properly
coated has the ability
to withstand almost any sort of pressure,
but it also has very little buoyancy.
The floating bag beneath the ship
is the only thing keeping us afloat.
By deflating it, the sunny will
become less buoyant and begin to sink.
It's pretty simple, really.
Huh, interesting.
Maybe not simple enough.
Forget about it for now.
Let's spread the sail.
Why?
We use it to catch the water current,
similar to how we would use
the wind above sea level.
I was hoping we'd just
sink down to fish man eye.
Darn.
All right!
We'd better hurry unless we
want to get in another fight!
This is Central Unit Platoon 5 at row 42.
We have an emergency!
The troops from Platoon 2 have been found,
but they've all succumbed
to a severe depression!
Tell him to suck it up
and get back in the fight!
I suck!
I should have been born a waterfall!
What we've been able to gather is that
Straw Hat Luffy flew off on a giant bird!
So he's not even there?
Then what are you guys shooting at?
We are currently under
attack by unknown enemies!
The enforcement's got here quick.
We were just about to leave.
Heads up!
The Straw Hat ship is now within range.
But we may have a problem.
A large bird is heading straight for us.
Oh, wow!
Uh, from behind, too?
I got it!
Like what you see, Nami?
I've gotten a lot stronger.
Go ahead and take it in.
No, not again!
Platoon 5, come in!
What's going on?
Well, it isn't good.
We've hit interference.
We couldn't possibly
have anticipated this.
Ah!
Have mercy!
How could you ever think of turning
beauties like us away, as if?
Maybe they're all shy.
There's nothing to be ashamed of, boys.
Let's have a cup of tea and cookies, too.
How awful.
Truly, this is worse than death.
Hi there.
You've got such an adorable face.
No, let me go.
What's wrong now?
Platoon 5, finish your report!
This is for you, Sanji. Make it count.
Whoa!
Take it easy, Sanji. Breathe!
Usopp, it's you.
Sorry, it felt like someone had
gotten a death grip on my heart.
Bag's deflated! Awesome.
You guys ready?
Yeah, we're all set.
That ain't it, Nami?
Yeah.
Just say the word, Captain.
All right.
Listen up, guys!
There's a lot I want to say,
but we don't have much time.
One thing can't wait, though.
What you went through these past
two years was selfish of me,
so thanks for putting up with it.
You make it sound like this
has never happened before.
That's no joke.
You've always been a
selfish piece of work.
Rear Admiral, the pirate
ship is submerging!
You can't wait!
Listen, you have no idea how
dangerous these pirates are!
Move your ship now, pretty
please! Yes, please!
Take care of yourself, Luffy.
Spread yourself!
Right!
Let's go!
Yeah!
We're up to Fishman Island!
We go!